

Sarah Fosse Norrköping, Sweden

Mail: sarah@sarahfosse.se

Birth: 920714



Personal summary

My name is Sarah Fosse and I am 24 years old. I am currently studying my 4th year of my M.Sc in Media Technology at Linköping University. I would describe myself as a positive, creative and committed person with a passion for technology.

Education

2013-now M.Sc in Media Technology, Linköping University, Norrköping

A Master of Science in Media Technology. The training includes extensive software programming, mathematics combined with creative subjects such as web design, visualization and image processing.

2012-2013 Advertising & Public Relations 60hp, Stockholm University, Stockholm

A basic course with focus on Advertising and PR. The course discussed media, consumer behavior and marketing.

Work history

2016-now Fit model, Stadium HQ, Norrköping

Work a few hours a week as a Fit model at the Stadium HQ which is a company that retail sports and leisurewear. I get to try on new clothing and give feedback about the garment.

2016 Customer care, Setsale AB, Stockholm

Handled incoming calls from subscribers of the morning paper Dagens Nyheter regarding their subscription and temporary change of address during the summer. I also became the expert on the office on transferring address segments between different postal areas.

2011-2012 Crew member, Burger King, Odenplan

Handled payment and food mostly. I was nominated employee of the month in December 2011.

Technical skills

- Microsoft Office (basic knowledge)
- Adobe (beginner)
 - Photoshop (beginner)
- C++ (basic knowledge)
- Java (basic knowledge)
- HTML, JavaScript and CSS (basic knowledge)
- Matlab (basic knowledge)
- Github (basic knowledge)

Language skills

- Swedish (native)
- English (fluent)
- Spanish (basic knowledge)

Commitments

Media Technology section

During 2015/2016 I was the Secretary and Working environment representative in the board of the Media Technology section. Besides the general Secretary work as taking minutes of meetings I was also responsible for organizing the fall- and spring meeting for our approximately 200 members together with the chairperson. As the Working Environment representative I took care of the student welfare and all working environment related issues concerning the section.

Reception & introduction of new students

During spring 2014 I had the opportunity to work with the reception and welcoming activities for new students in the section. I was responsible for all the scheduled activities during the two first weeks for the new students, a work that is done together across sections to create a great introduction for new students. Thanks to a well-organized reception our campus has previously been elected the best student city in Sweden by Swedes united student unions (Sveriges förenade studentkårer) in 2013.

Other

Spare time

I like to spend time with friends on my spare time. I also like to work out and paint and take photos.